A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Institutional Grants and Proposals, 1983-1998; 2
  - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Grant 88-46 (Reel 97, Frame 106)
  - University of Michigan, Ann Arbor - Grant 96-7 (Reel 97, Frame 586)
  - Michigan Cancer Foundation - Denied Proposal 90-25 (Reel 97, Frame 620)
  - Michigan Technological Unviersity - Denied Proposal 89-41 (Reel 97, Frame 629)
  - University of Minnesota - Denied Proposals 85-105, 88-37, 89-20, 90-36 (Reel 97, Frame 645)
  - University of Mississippi - Denied Proposals 85-178, 85-211 (Reel 97, Frame 731)
  - University of Missouri - Denied Proposals 87-22, 89-3 (Reel 97, Frame 835)
  - Montana State University - Denied Proposal 88-78 (Reel 97, Frame 897)
  - Montefiore Hospital - Denied Proposals 86-106, 86-107, 86-108, 86-109, 86-110, 86-111 (Reel 97, Frame 926)
  - (H. E.) Moore Heart Foundation - Denied Proposal 85-49 (Reel 97, Frame 952)
  - Morehouse School - General Correspondence (Reel 97, Frame 967)
  - Mote Marine Laboratory - Denied Proposals 85-15, 85-214, 92-65 (Reel 97, Frame 969)
  - Mount Desert Island Biological Laboratory - Denied Proposal 93-6 (Reel 97, Frame 1059)
  - Mount Desert Island Biological Laboratory - Grant 85-20 (Reel 98, Frame 1)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center - Denied Proposals 84-48, 86-93 (Reel 98, Frame 806)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center - Grant 93-2 (Reel 99, Frame 1)
  - Mount Sinai Medical Center Foundation - Denied Proposal 88-47 (Reel 99, Frame 247)
  - Nassau County Medical Center - Denied Proposal 88-47 (Reel 99, Frame 267)
  - National Academy of Sciences - General Correspondence (Reel 99, Frame 279)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Denied Proposals 84-44, 91-33, 91-41, 94-33, 97-6 (Reel 99, Frame 298)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Grant 88-10 (Reel 99, Frame 368)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Grant 90-44 (Reel 99, Frame 474)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Grant 90-45 (Reel 99, Frame 644)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Grant 93-8 (Reel 99, Frame 752)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Grant 97-2 (Reel 99, Frame 809)
  - National Academy of Sciences - Grant 98-1 (Reel 99, Frame 880)
  - National Cancer Institute - General Correspondence (Reel 99, Frame 1006)
  - National Center for the Study of Wilson's Disease, Inc. - Grant 98-7 (Reel 99, Frame 1008)
  - National Center for the Study of Wilson's Disease, Inc. - Grant 98-7 (Reel 100, Frame 1)
  - National Council on Alcoholism, Inc. - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 16)
  - National Institutes of Health - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 19)
  - National Jewish Center for Immunology and Respiratory Medicine - Denied Proposals 86-74, 89-49 (Reel 100, Frame 86)
  - National Jewish Hospital and Research Center, National Asthma Center - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 116)
  - National Medical Fellowships, Inc. - Denied Proposal 90-69 (Reel 100, Frame 134)
  - National Society to Prevent Blindness - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 167)
  - University of Nebraska Foundation - Denied Proposal 94-36 (Reel 100, Frame 170)
  - University of Nebraska Medical Center - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 190)
  - University of Nebraska Medical Center - Denied Proposals 85-120, 85-135, 85-161, 85-230, 87-40, 92-16 (Reel 100, Frame 200)
  - Neuroscience Study Center - Denied Proposal 84-38 (Reel 100, Frame 259)
  - Neurosciences Institute - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 280)
  - Neurosciences Institute - Grant 88-48 (Reel 100, Frame 283)
  - University of Nevada, Las Vegas - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 526)
  - University of Nevada, Reno - Denied Proposals 89-1, 89-47 (Reel 100, Frame 529)
  - New England Deaconess Hospital - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 577)
  - New England Medical Center, Inc. - Denied Proposal 89-6 (Reel 100, Frame 593)
  - State University of New Jersey, Rutgers - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 627)
  - State University of New Jersey, Rutgers - Denied Proposals 85-136, 85-192, 85-202, 86-100, 88-39 (Reel 100, Frame 647)
  - New Jersey University of Medicine and Dentistry - Robert Wood Johnson Medical School - Denied Proposals 85-58, 86-140, 87-10, 87-12, 87-26, 88-16, 89-91 (Reel 100, Frame 748)
  - University of New Mexico School of Medicine, Albuquerque - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 868)
  - University of New Mexico School of Medicine, Albuquerque - Denied Proposals 86-29, 88-38 (Reel 100, Frame 881)
  - New Mexico State University - Denied Poposal 86-166 (Reel 100, Frame 937)
  - Research Foundation of the State University of New York - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 951)
  - State University of New York, Albany - Denied Proposal 85-168 (Reel 100, Frame 954)
  - State University of New York, Binghamton - Denied Proposal 89-76 (Reel 100, Frame 963)
  - State University of New York, Buffalo - General Correspondence (Reel 100, Frame 980)
  - State University of New York, Buffalo - Denied Proposals 86-102, 88-19, 89-48 (Reel 100, Frame 990)
  - State University of New York, Buffalo - Grant 95-27 (Reel 101, Frame 1)
  - State University of New York, Downstate Medical Center - Denied Proposals 85-165, 86-44, 89-28, 91-29 (Reel 101, Frame 157)
  - State University of New York, Stony Brook - Denied Proposals 85-166, 91-25, 94-22 (Reel 101, Frame 230)
  - State University of New York, Upstate Medical Center - General Correspondence (Reel 101, Frame 275)
  - State University of New York, Upstate Medical Center - Denied Proposals 85-242, 86-8 (Reel 101, Frame 285)
  - New York Academy of Medicine - Grant 91-45 (Reel 101, Frame 340)
  - New York Academy of Sciences - Denied Proposal 96-1 (Reel 101, Frame 383)
  - New York Academy of Sciences - Grant 95-17 (Reel 101, Frame 418)
  - New York Blood Center - General Correspondence (Reel 101, Frame 537)
  - New York Blood Center - Denied Proposal 88-62 (Reel 101, Frame 578)
  - New York Institute of Technology - Denied Proposal 89-30 (Reel 101, Frame 589)
  - New York Medical College - Denied Proposal 90-2 (Reel 101, Frame 605)
  - New York State Department of Health and Health Research, Inc. - Denied Proposals 89-24, 89-44 (Reel 101, Frame 623)
  - New York University - General Correspondence (Reel 101, Frame 665)
  - New York University - Denied Proposals 85-50, 85-278, 87-14, 87-67, 92-60 (Reel 101, Frame 703)
  - New York University - Grant 91-4 (Reel 101, Frame 761)
  - New York University - Grant 98-3 (Reel 101, Frame 991)
  - University of Newcastle Upon Tyne - General Correspondence (Reel 102, Frame 1)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - General Correspondence (Reel 102, Frame 4)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Denied Proposals 85-176, 86-99, 86-131, 86-136, 86-141, 86-146, 87-61, 89-79, 90-68 (Reel 102, Frame 20)
  - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Grant 95-5 (Reel 102, Frame 212)
  - North Carolina State University - General Correspondence (Reel 102, Frame 332)
  - University of North Dakota, Grand Forks - Denied Proposal 91-8 (Reel 102, Frame 337)
  - North Texas State University - Denied Proposal 86-14 (Reel 102, Frame 368)
  - Northwestern University - General Correspondence (Reel 102, Frame 375)
  - Northwestern University - Denied Proposals 85-113, 85-115, 85-201, 85-218, 85-277 (Reel 102, Frame 406)
  - Northwestern University - Grant 84-8 (Reel 102, Frame 474)
  - Northwestern University - Grant 89-28 (Reel 102, Frame 619)
  - Northwestern University - (Supplement to Grant 89-28) - Grant 96-13 (Reel 103, Frame 1)
  - University of Notre Dame - General Correspondence (Reel 103, Frame 28)
  - University of Notre Dame - Denied Proposals 84-221, 85-107, 88-54, 90-42 (Reel 103, Frame 54)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities - Denied Proposal 88-83 (Reel 103, Frame 121)
  - Medical College of Ohio - Denied Proposal 86-2 (Reel 103, Frame 135)
  - Ohio State University - General Correspondence (Reel 103, Frame 150)
  - Ohio State University - Denied Proposals 86-5, 89-33 (Reel 103, Frame 173)
  - University of Oklahoma, Oklahoma City - Denied Proposals 85-72, 87-32 (Reel 103, Frame 210)
  - Oklahoma Medical Research Foundation - General Correspondence (Reel 103, Frame 240)
  - Oklahoma State University - Denied Proposals 86-53, 86-54, 86-55, 86-56, 86-124 (Reel 103, Frame 250)
  - University of Oregon - Grant 88-16 (Reel 103, Frame 297)
  - Oregon Graduate Center - Denied Proposal 88-18 (Reel 103, Frame 504)
  - Oregon Health Sciences University - Denied Proposal 97-1 (Reel 103, Frame 529)
  - Oregon Health Sciences University - Grant 95-10 (Reel 103, Frame 532)
  - Oregon State University - Deneid Proposals 85-133, 85-169, 85-190, 87-62 (Reel 103, Frame 672)
  - Orton Dyslexia Society - Denied Proposal 85-139 (Reel 103, Frame 730)
  - Oxford University - Denied Proposal 91-31 (Reel 103, Frame 740)
  - Medical College of Pennsylvania - Denied Proposal 85-195 (Reel 103, Frame 770)
  - University of Pennsylvania - General Correspondence (Reel 103, Frame 803)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Denied Proposals 84-177, 84-206, 85-6, 85-9, 85-11, 85-14, 85-210, 85-223, 85-224, 86-113, 87-33, 91-9, 92-36, 94-3 (Reel 103, Frame 844)
  - University of Pennsylvania - Grant 88-21 (Reel 104, Frame 1)
  - University of Pennsylvania - (Supplement to Grant 88-21) - Grant 97-8 (Reel 104, Frame 626)
  - Pennsylvania State University - Denied Proposals 88-24, 88-7 (Reel 104, Frame 648)
  - University of Pittsburgh - General Correspondence (Reel 104, Frame 708)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Denied Proposals 84-144, 85-200, 86-73, 87-28, 90-20 (Reel 104, Frame 742)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Grant 85-14 (Reel 104, Frame 834)
  - Planned Parenthood of Sacramento Valley - Denied Proposal 85-154 (Reel 105, Frame 1)
  - Pohl Cancer Research Laboratory, Inc. - Denied Proposal 85-63 (Reel 105, Frame 23)
  - Portland State University - Denied Proposal 85-137 (Reel 105, Frame 40)
  - Princeton University - General Correspondence (Reel 105, Frame 46)
  - Princeton University - Denied Proposals 84-208, 85-76, 85-189 (Reel 105, Frame 69)
  - Princeton University - Grant 92-25 (Reel 105, Frame 144)
  - Psoriasis Research Institute - Denied Proposal 85-216 (Reel 105, Frame 354)
  - Public Health Research Institute of The City of New York, Inc. - Denied Proposal 85-180 (Reel 105, Frame 380)
  - Public Health Research Institute of The City of New York, Inc. - Grant 92-23 (Reel 105, Frame 393)
  - Purdue University - Denied Proposals 85-251, 86-169, 89-60, 90-28 (Reel 105, Frame 770)
  - Purdue University - Grant 88-60 (Reel 106, Frame 1)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Denied Proposals 86-19, 86-35, 90-53 (Reel 106, Frame 499)
  - Research! America - General Correspondence (Reel 106, Frame 534)
  - Research! America - Grant 90-36 (Reel 106, Frame 545)
  - Research to Prevent Blindness - General Correspondence (Reel 106, Frame 788)
  - Research to Prevent Blindness - Grant 84-2 (Reel 106, Frame 875)
  - Rice University - Denied Proposals 85-68, 88-79 (Reel 107, Frame 1)
  - Rice University - Grant 95-23 (Reel 107, Frame 56)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology - Denied Proposal 91-34 (Reel 107, Frame 164)
  - University of Rochester Medical Center - General Correspondence (Reel 107, Frame 188)
  - University of Rochester Medical Center - Grant 91-24 (Reel 107, Frame 203)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center - General Correspondence (Reel 107, Frame 520)
  - Rockefeller University - General Correspondence (Reel 107, Frame 589)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 84-9 (Reel 107, Frame 712)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 85-22 (Reel 108, Frame 1)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 86-1 (Reel 108, Frame 136)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 89-29 (Reel 108, Frame 318)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 90-42 (Reel 108, Frame 558)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 91-14 (Reel 108, Frame 586)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 93-14 (Reel 108, Frame 678)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 93-20 (Reel 108, Frame 852)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 96-8 (Reel 108, Frame 879)
  - Rockefeller University - Grant 98-4 (Reel 108, Frame 924)
  - Rogosin Institute - Denied Proposal 92-62 (Reel 109, Frame 1)
  - Roswell Park Memorial Institute - Denied Proposals 85-109, 85-110, 85-186, 86-67, 87-45, 88-11, 88-12, 88-31, 88-58, 88-8 (Reel 109, Frame 16)
  - Royal Society of Medicine - Denied Proposal 89-13 (Reel 109, Frame 125)
  - Rush-Presbyterian St. Luke's Medical Center - Grant 95-24 (Reel 109, Frame 138)
  - Salk Institute - Denied Proposals 85-55, 85-150 (Reel 109, Frame 313)
  - Salk Institute - Grant 92-26 (Reel 109, Frame 328)
  - Salk Institute - Grant 94-13 (Reel 109, Frame 387)
  - Salzburg Seminar - Denied Proposal 93-9 (Reel 109, Frame 517)
  - Samsum Medical Research Foundation - Denied Proposal 92-33 (Reel 109, Frame 541)
  - University of San Diego - General Correspondence (Reel 109, Frame 551)
  - Santa Fe Institute - Denied Proposal 89-54 (Reel 109, Frame 555)
  - Schepens Eye Research Institute - Grant 95-25 (Reel 109, Frame 606)
  - Schneider Children's Hospital of Long Island Jewish Medical Center - Denied Proposal 85-219 (Reel 109, Frame 794)
  - Scientists' Institute for Public Information - Denied Proposal 90-59 (Reel 109, Frame 804)
  - Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation - Denied Proposal 85-244 (Reel 109, Frame 854)
  - Scripps Research Institute - Grant 92-10 (Reel 109, Frame 871)
  - Scripps Research Institute - Grant 92-32 (Reel 110, Frame 1)
  - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society - General Correspondence (Reel 110, Frame 55)
  - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society - Grant 93-7 (Reel 110, Frame 87)
  - Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society - Grant 95-33 (Reel 110, Frame 151)
  - Sinai Hospital of Detroit - Denied Proposal 85-160 (Reel 110, Frame 182)
  - Smith-Kettlewell Eye Research Foundation - Denied Proposal 86-162 (Reel 110, Frame 188)
  - Smithsonian Institution - Denied Proposal 85-259 (Reel 110, Frame 197)
  - Society of General Physiologists, Inc. - Grant 90-43 (Reel 110, Frame 246)
  - Unviersity of South Alabama - Denied Proposal 91-36 (Reel 110, Frame 307)
  - Medical University of South Carolina - Denied Proposal 85-235 (Reel 110, Frame 346)
  - University of South Carolina - Denied Proposals 85-151, 85-235, 86-115 (Reel 110, Frame 370)
  - University of South Florida - General Correspondence (Reel 110, Frame 390)
  - University of South Florida - Denied Proposals 85-59, 93-32 (Reel 110, Frame 444)
  - University of South Florida Health Sciences Center - Grant 92-18 (Reel 110, Frame 496)
  - Cancer Therapy & Research Foundation of South Texas - Denied Proposal 86-151 (Reel 110, Frame 577)
  - University of Southern California - Denied Proposal 85-54 (Reel 110, Frame 585)
  - University of Southern California - Grant 94-16 (Reel 110, Frame 615)
  - Southern Illinois University - Denied Proposals 85-153, 86-34, 88-59 (Reel 110, Frame 784)
  - Southern Methodist University - Denied Proposal 89-52 (Reel 110, Frame 830)
  - Southwest Biomedical Research Institute - Denied Proposals 89-84, 91-38 (Reel 110, Frame 854)
  - Southwest Foundation for Biomedical Research - Denied Proposals 86-17, 86-85 (Reel 110, Frame 892)
  - Spinal Cord Society - Denied Proposal 86-51 (Reel 110, Frame 915)
  - St. Jude's Children's Research Hospital - Denied Proposals 86-86, 86-89, 86-132 (Reel 110, Frame 928)
  - St. Luke's/Roosevelt Hospital Center - Denied Proposal 87-49 (Reel 110, Frame 985)
  - Stanford University - General Correspondence (Reel 111, Frame 1)
  - Stanford University - Denied Proposals 88-23, 89-5, 95-12 (Reel 111, Frame 83)
  - Stanford University - Grant 84-10 (Reel 111, Frame 115)
  - Stanford University - Grant 85-1 (Reel 111, Frame 279)
  - Stanford University - Grant 86-6 (Reel 111, Frame 340)
  - Stanford University - Grant 86-7 (Reel 111, Frame 373)
  - Stanford University - Grant 88-56 (Reel 111, Frame 696)
  - Stanford University - Grant 90-40 (Reel 111, Frame 724)
  - Stanford University - Grant 91-15 (Reel 111, Frame 805)
  - Stanford University - Grant 91-46 (Reel 112, Frame 1)
  - Stanford University - Grant 93-13 (Reel 112, Frame 77)
  - Stanford University - Grant 93-21 (Reel 112, Frame 266)
  - Stanford University - Grant 95-26 (Reel 112, Frame 317)
  - Stanford University - Grant 96-9 (Reel 112, Frame 390)
  - University of Sydney - General Correspondence (Reel 112, Frame 422)
  - Tampa Bay Research Institute - Denied Proposals 92-41, 94-23 (Reel 112, Frame 425)
  - Teachers Academy for Mathematics and Science - Denied Proposals 92-47, 92-54 (Reel 112, Frame 449)
  - Temple University - Denied Proposals 85-253, 88-15 (Reel 112, Frame 486)
  - Temple University - Grant 90-11 (Reel 112, Frame 582)
  - University of Tennessee Center for Health Sciences - General Correspondence (Reel 112, Frame 868)
  - University of Tennessee, Knoxville - Denied Proposals 89-4, 89-7 (Reel 112, Frame 881)
  - University of Tennessee, Memphis - Denied Proposals 85-2, 85-28, 85-29, 85-114, 85-141, 90-40, 91-4 (Reel 112, Frame 913)
  - University of Texas, Arlington - General Correspondence (Reel 113, Frame 1)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Denied Proposals 85-48, 88-45 (Reel 113, Frame 29)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Dallas - General Correspondence (Reel 113, Frame 76)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Dallas - Denied Proposals 84-47, 85-238, 86-9, 93-25 (Reel 113, Frame 116)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston - General Correspondence (Reel 113, Frame 152)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston - Denied Proposals 84-48, 85-130, 85-149, 85-175, 86-84, 87-50, 88-2, 8-30, 89-89, 90-34, 91-24, 92-6 (Reel 113, Frame 167)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston - Grant 95-29 (Reel 113, Frame 315)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio - General Correspondence (Reel 113, Frame 497)
  - University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antonio - Denied Proposals 85-47, 85-159, 86-47, 86-71, 89-51 (Reel 113, Frame 502)
  - University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston - Denied Proposals 85-65, 85-66, 85-67, 85-96, 85-122, 86-129, 87-70, 90-39 (Reel 113, Frame 549)
  - University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston - Grant 95-6 (Reel 113, Frame 620)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center - Grant 86-2 (Reel 113, Frame 758)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center - Grant 88-20 (Reel 113, Frame 865)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center - Grant 92-5 (Reel 114, Frame 1)
  - University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center - Grant 96-5 (Reel 114, Frame 158)
  - University of Texas, Tyler - Denied Proposal 86-123 (Reel 114, Frame 197)
  - Texas A&M University - Denied Proposals 89-26, 89-83 (Reel 114, Frame 230)
  - Texas A&M University - Grant 95-28 (Reel 114, Frame 275)
  - Texas College of Osteopathic Medicine - Denied Proposal 86-161 (Reel 114, Frame 381)
  - Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center - Denied Proposals 85-44, 89-17, 90-58 (Reel 114, Frame 391)
  - Thomas Jefferson University - Denied Proposal 86-88 (Reel 114, Frame 458)
  - Thomas Jefferson University - Grant 90-9 (Reel 114, Frame 494)
  - Thomas More College - Denied Proposal 89-92 (Reel 114, Frame 677)
  - Transylvania University - General Correspondence (Reel 114, Frame 691)
  - Trulson Brain Research Foundation, Inc. - Denied Proposal 86-60 (Reel 114, Frame 697)
  - Tufts University - General Correspondence (Reel 114, Frame 708)
  - Tufts University - Denied Proposals 85-77, 86-181, 85-207, 86-30, 86-57, 86-94, 87-37, 89-66 (Reel 114, Frame 733)
  - Tufts University - Grant 90-17 (Reel 115, Frame 1)
  - Tufts University - Grant 93-5 (Reel 115, Frame 251)
  - Tulane University Medical Center - General Correspondence (Reel 115, Frame 434)
  - University of Tulsa - General Correspondence (Reel 115, Frame 447)
  - University City Science Center - Denied Proposal 86-105 (Reel 115, Frame 450)
  - University of Utah, Salt Lake City - Denied Proposals 85-198, 86-65, 86-127, 86-164, 88-4 (Reel 115, Frame 499)
  - University of Utah, Salt Lake City - Grant 93-3 (Reel 115, Frame 573)
  - University of Utah, Salt Lake City - Grant 94-5 (Reel 115, Frame 707)
  - Vanderbilt University - Denied Proposals 85-23, 86-1, 86-143, 90-50, 92-30 (Reel 115, Frame 860)
  - Vanderbilt University - Grant 91-16 (Reel 116, Frame 1)
  - Vanderbilt University - Grant 97-9 (Reel 116, Frame 194)
  - Varsity Children's Hospital - General Correspondence (Reel 116, Frame 217)
  - Vassar College - General Correspondence (Reel 116, Frame 219)
  - Vassar College - Denied Proposal 88-40 (Reel 116, Frame 272)
  - Vassar College - Grant 88-49 (Reel 116, Frame 323)
  - University of Vermont, Burlington - Grant 91-6 (Reel 116, Frame 470)
  - Veterans Adminsitration Hospital, Illinois - Denied Proposals 89-93, 89-95 (Reel 116, Frame 765)
  - Veterans Adminsitration Medical Center - Denied Proposal 87-15 (Reel 116, Frame 777)
  - Medical College of Virginia - General Correspondence (Reel 116, Frame 798)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville - General Correspondence (Reel 116, Frame 802)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville - Denied Proposals 84-131, 85-10, 85-20, 86-52, 89-55 (Reel 116, Frame 871)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville - Grant 90-10 (Reel 117, Frame 1)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville - Grant 92-36 (Reel 117, Frame 379)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville - Grant 93-12 (Reel 117, Frame 481)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville - Supplement to Grant 93-12 (Reel 117, Frame 609)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - Denied Proposals 85-115, 85-203, 90-19, 92-37 (Reel 117, Frame 622)
  - Virginia-Maryland Regional College of Veterinary Medicine - Denied Proposal 86-171 (Reel 117, Frame 700)
  - Virginia Mason Medical Foundation - General Correspondence (Reel 117, Frame 715)
  - Virginia-Polytechnic Institute and State University - Denied Proposal 89-65 (Reel 117, Frame 720)
  - Wake Forest University - Denied Proposals 88-68, 90-23, 92-58 (Reel 117, Frame 731)
  - University of Washington, Seattle - General Correspondence (Reel 117, Frame 767)
  - University of Washington, Seattle - Denied Proposals 86-172, 86-176 (Reel 117, Frame 820)
  - University of Washington, Seattle - Grant 90-12 (Reel 117, Frame 835)
  - Washington State University - Denied Proposals 85-156, 85-171, 85-232, 88-67, 90-3, 90-17 (Reel 118, Frame 1)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - Denied Proposals 84-250, 85-80-85-148, 86-3, 97-12 (Reel 118, Frame 56)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - Grant 84-17 (Reel 118, Frame 187)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - Grant 88-12 (Reel 118, Frame 360)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - Grant 92-3 (Reel 118, Frame 784)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - Grant 96-10 (Reel 119, Frame 1)
  - Washington University in St. Louis - Grant 98-2 (Reel 119, Frame 39)
  - Wayne State University School of Medicine - General Correspondence (Reel 119, Frame 57)
  - Wayne State University School of Medicine - Denied Proposals 84-200, 88-84 (Reel 119, Frame 65)
  - Webb-Waring Lung Institute - Denied Proposal 89-71 (Reel 119, Frame 88)
  - West Virginia University - Denied Proposals 85-126, 86-39 (Reel 119, Frame 103)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Denied Proposal 95-10 (Reel 119, Frame 124)
  - WGBH Educational Foundation - Grant 90-16 (Reel 119, Frame 182)
  - Whitehead Institute - Denied Proposals 92-35, 93-18 (Reel 119, Frame 420)
  - Whitehead Institute - Grant 88-11 (Reel 119, Frame 519)
  - Whitehead Institute - Grant 96-12 (Reel 119, Frame 846)
  - Whitney/Childs/Life Sciences Foundation - Denied Proposal 90-6 (Reel 119, Frame 877)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison - General Correspondence (Reel 119, Frame 907)